Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Central Region Freight Joint Area Committee Transcript Records 1954-2010 IBT0053
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Central Region Freight Joint Area Committee Transcript Records
1954-2010
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT0053
115.5 Linear Feet
This collection consists of typed stenographic notes relating to the Central Confernece of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. The articles include committee meetings, contract negotiations, grievance hearings, change of operations statuses and discharge cases under the National Master Freight Agreeement. The articles range in date from 1954-2010.
For many Change of Operation Committee Meeting transcripts, there are sizable gaps in the records.
Biographical
This collection was created by the Central Conference of Teamsters. The Conference consisted of Local Unions and State Councils from the Midwestern United States. Many of the documents were created in Chicago, IL. Over time they were housed at Teamster headquarters in Washington, DC. In 2014, they were transferred to The George Washington University where they remain today.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series. It is arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
This collections consists of typed stenographic notes relating to the activities of the Central Conference. The documents range in date from 1954-2010. The articles include committee meetings, contract negotiations, grievance hearings, change of operations statuses and discharge cases under the National Master Freight Agreement. The Agreement was signed in 1964 between the Teamsters and individual trucking companies. Teamsters General President James R. Hoffa played a large role in the Agreement's passage. The contract established rules and regulations for freight industry employees. It also created uniform wages and working conditions for truck drivers, warehousemen and dockworkers throughout America.
- Council Meeting, 1954, November 8 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Union Meeting, 1954, November 8 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Freight Agreement Meeting, 1954, November 9 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- City Cartage Meeting, 1954, November 11 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1954, December 7 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- City Cartage Meeting, 1954, December 15 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Over-the-Road Freight Meeting [1 of 3], 1955, January 10-21 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Over-the-Road Freight Meeting [2 of 3], 1955, January 10-21 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Over-the-Road Freight Meeting [3 of 3], 1955, January 10-21 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1955, March 15 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Council Meeting, 1955, March 16-17 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting, 1955, March 17 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1955, June 14-15 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Committee Meeting, 1955, June 15-16 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1955, September 13 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Committee Meeting, 1955, September 14-15 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Council Meeting, 1955, September 15 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Excerpt of Committee Meeting, 1955, September 15 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1955, December 6 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Committee Meeting, 1955, December 8 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Council Meeting, 1955, December 8 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Executive Board Meeting, 1955, December 8 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Committee Meeting, 1955, December 8 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1956, March 6-8 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Committee Meeting, 1956, March 7-8 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- 24-Man Board and Committee Meeting, 1956, June 11 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1956, June 12 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Committee Meeting, 1956, June 13-14 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Preliminary Meeting, 1956, September 10 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1956, September 11-13 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Committee Meeting, 1956, September 12-13 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1956, December 3-4 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Committee Meeting, 1956, December 5 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1957, March 4-5 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Committee Meeting, 1957, March 6 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1957, June 10-13 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1957, June 12-13 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1957, June 12-13 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1957, September 9-12 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1957, September 11-12 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1957, September 11-12 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Council Meeting, 1957, October 29 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Council Meeting, 1957, October 29 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Council Meeting, 1957, October 29 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Drafting Committee Meeting, 1957, November 14 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Freight Amendment Meeting, 1957, November 21 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1957, December 9 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Council Meeting, 1957, December 10 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Committee Meeting, 1957, December 10 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Committee Meeting, 1957, December 11-12 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Union Meeting, 1957, December 16 & 29 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Cartage Negotiation Meeting [1 of 2], 1957, December 16, 27-29 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Cartage Negotiation Meeting [2 of 2], 1957, December 16, 27-29 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1958, March 10 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1958, March 11 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1958, March 12 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1958, March 12 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1958, March 12 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Building Committee Meeting, 1958, April 15 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1958, June 9-10 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1958, June 11-12 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1958, June 11-12 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1958, June 11-12 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Executive Board Meeting, 1958, July 7 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1958, September 8 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1958, September 9 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1958, September 10 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1958, September 10 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1958, September 10 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Misc. Meeting, Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1958, December 1 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Council Meeting, 1958, December 2 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1958, December 3-4 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1958, December 3-4 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1958, December 3-4 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1959, March 16 & 19 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1959, March 18-19 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1959, March 18-19 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1959, March 18-19 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Case Number 52 Meeting, 1959, March 19 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Council Meeting, 1959, June 16 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- City Cartage Meeting, 1959, June 17 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1959, September 14 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Council Meeting, 1959, September 15 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1959, September 15-17 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1959, September 15-17 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1959, September 15-17 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1959, September 15-17 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1959, September 15-17 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1959, September 15-17 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1959, November 30 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Council Meeting, 1959, December 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1959, December 1-3 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1959, December 1-3 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1959, December 1-3 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Over-the-Road Meeting [1 of 3], 1960, March (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Over-the-Road Meeting [2 of 3], 1960, March (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Over-the-Road Meeting [3 of 3], 1960, March (Box 11, Folder 7)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1960, March 14 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Council Meeting, 1960, March 15 & 17 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting [1 of 2], 1960, March 15 & 17 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Council Meeting [2 of 2], 1960, March 15 & 17 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1960, March 15-17 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1960, March 15-17 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1960, March 15-17 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1960, June 13 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Council Meeting, 1960, June 14 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1960, June 14-16 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1960, June 14-16 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1960, June 14-16 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Council Meeting, 1960, June 16 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1960, September 19 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Council Meeting, 1960, September 19 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1960, September 20-21 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1960, September 20-21 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1960, September 20-21 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Local Cartage Meeting, 1960, September 20-21 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Council Meeting, 1960, September 21 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Special Meeting, 1960, October 20 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1960, December 5 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Council Meeting, 1960, December 5 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Meeting, 1960, December 6 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1960, December 6-7 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1960, December 6-7 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1960, December 6-7 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1961, March 6 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Council Meeting, 1961, March 6 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Meeting, 1961, March 7-8 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1961, March 7-10 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1961, March 7-10 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1961, March 7-10 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Council Meeting, 1961, March 10 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1961, June 12 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Council Meeting, 1961, June 12 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Meeting [1 of 2], 1961, June 13 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Meeting [2 of 2], 1961, June 13 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1961, June 13 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1961, June 13 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1961, June 13-15 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1961, June 13-15 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1961, June 13-15 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- 24-Man Board Meeting, 1961, September 18 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Council Meeting, 1961, September 18 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Executive Board Meeting, 1961, September 18 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1961, September 19-20 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1961, September 19-20 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1961, September 19-21 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1961, September 19-21 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1961, September 19-21 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Local Cartage Meeting, 1961, September 19 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Council Meeting, 1961, December 11 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Meeting, 1961, December 12 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting, 1961, December 12-13 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1961, December 12-15 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1961, December 12-15 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1961, December 12-15 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Special Meeting, 1962, February 28 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Council Meeting, 1962, March 26 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Meeting, 1962, March 26 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Change-of-Operations Meeting, 1962, March 27-29 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1962, March 27-29 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1962, March 27-29 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1962, March 27-29 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Joint Committee Meeting, 1962, March 28 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Special Committee Meeting, 1962, March 28 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Council Meeting, 1962, June 11 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Joint Commodity Committee Meeting, 1962, June 12 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Meeting, 1962, June 12-13 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1962, June 12-14 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1962, June 12-14 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1962, June 12-14 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Council Meeting, 1962, September 17 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Joint Special Commodity Meeting, 1962, September 18 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Change-of-Operations Meeting, 1962, September 18-19 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1962, September 18-20 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1962, September 18-20 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1962, September 18-20 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Meeting, 1962, September 18-20 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Council Meeting, 1963, January 7 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Meeting [1 of 2], 1963, January 8 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Meeting [2 of 2], 1963, January 8 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Special Commodity Meeting, 1963, January 8 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting, 1963, January 8-9 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Meeting [1 of 2], 1963, Januaury 8-10 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Meeting [2 of 2], 1963, January 8-10 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1963, January 8-10 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1963, January 8-10 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1963, January 8-10 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Transamerican Meeting, 1963, January 10 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Western Transportation Meeting, 1963, January 10 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting, 1963, March 18 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting, 1963, March 19 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Special Commodity Meeting, 1963, March 19 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Transamerican Cases Meeting, 1963, March 19-20 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Meeting [1 of 2], 1963, March 19-20 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Change of Operations Meeting [2 of 2], 1963, March 19-20 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting, 1963, March 19-20 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Local Cartage Meeting, 1963, March 19-21 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Western Cases Meeting, 1963, March 20 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting, 1963, June 24 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Joint Commodity Meeting, 1963, June 25 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Joint Commodity Meeting, 1963, June 25 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Meeting, 1963, June 25-27 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1963, June 25-27 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1963, June 25-27 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1963, June 25-27 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting, 1963, September 16 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1963, September 17-18 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Special Commodities Meeting, 1963, September 17-18 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Change-of-Operations Meeting, 1963, September 17-18 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Transamerican Cases Meeting, 1963, September 18 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1963, September 17-19 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1963, September 17-19 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1963, September 17-19 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting, 1963, December 9 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Steel, Transamerican and Western Meeting, 1963, December 10-11 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1963, December 10-12 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1963, December 10-12 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1963, December 10-11 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1963, December 10-11 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting, 1964, March 16 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Committee Meeting, 1964, March 16 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1964, March 17-19 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1964, March 17-19 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1964, March 17-18 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1964, March 17-18 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [1 of 2], 1964, March 17-18 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [2 of 2], 1964, March 17-18 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting, 1964, June 15 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Change-of-Operations Meeting, 1964, June 16-17 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [1 of 2], 1964, June 16-17 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [2 of 2], 1964, June 16-17 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1964, June 16-17 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1964, June 16-17 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1964, June 16-18 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1964, June 16-18 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1964, June 16-18 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Council Meeting, 1964, September 21 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Council Meeting, 1964, September 21 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1964, September 22-23 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1964, September 22-23 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1964, September 22-24 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1964, September 22-24 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1964, September 22-24 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1964, September 22-24 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Multi-Conference Meeting, 1964, December 15 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Change-of-Operations Meeting, 1964, December 15-16 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1964, December 15-16 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1964, December 15-16 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Joint Steel and Review Board Meeting [1 of 2], 1964, December 15-16 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Joint Steel and Review Board Meeting [2 of 2], 1964, December 15-16 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1964, December 15-17 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1964, December 15-17 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Transamerican Cases Meeting, 1964, December 16 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Council Meeting, 1965, March 15 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Iron, Steel and Special Commodities Meeting, 1965, March 16 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1965, March 16-17 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1965, March 16-17 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Transamerican Freight Meeting, 1965, March 17 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Change-of-Operations Meeting, 1965, March 16-18 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1965, March 16-18 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1965, March 16-18 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting, 1965, June 14 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting, 1965, June 15-16 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1965, June 15-16 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1965, June 15-16 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1965, June 15-16 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1965, June 15-17 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1965, June 15-17 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Transamerican Cases Meeting, 1965, June 16 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Council Meeting, 1965, September 20 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1965, September 21-22 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1965, September 21-22 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1965, September 21-22 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1965, September 21-22 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1965, September 21-22 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1965, September 21-23 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Council Meeting, 1965, December 13 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1965, December 14-15 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1965, December 14-15 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1965, December 14-15 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1965, December 14-15 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting, 1965, December 14-15 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1965, December 15 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Refrigeration Committee Meeting, 1965, December 15 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Transamerican Cases Meeting, 1965, December 16 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Council Meeting, 1966, March 14 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting, 1966, March 15 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Change of Operations Commitee Meeting, 1966, March 15-16 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1966, March 15-16 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1966, March 15-16 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1966, March 15-16 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1966, March 15-16 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1966, March 16 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Perishable Commodities Meeting, 1966, March 16 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Transamerican Cases Meeting, 1966, March 17 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting, 1966, June 13 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1966, June 14 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1966, June 14-16 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1966, June 14-16 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1966, June 14-16 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1966, June 14-16 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1966, June 14-16 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1966, June 14-16 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1966, June 14-16 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Meeting, 1966, September 13-14 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Council Meeting, 1966, September 19 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1966, September 20-21 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [1 of 2], 1966, September 20-21 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [2 of 2], 1966, September 20-21 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Transamerican Cases Meeting, 1966, September 21 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1966, September 21-22 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1966, September 21-22 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Council Meeting, 1966, December 12 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Meeting [1 of 2], 1966, December 13-14 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Change of Operations Meeting [2 of 2], 1966, December 13-14 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1966, December 13-14 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1966, December 13-14 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Joint Steel Committee Meeting, 1966, December 13-14 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1966, December 14-15 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1966, December 14-15 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Council Meeting, 1967, March 20 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Meeting, 1967, March 21 (Box 43, Folder 2)